berlinpackaging.com 2016-12-31

# Privacy Policy

## Privacy Policy

Berlin Packaging  
525 West Monroe Street  
Chicago, IL 60661  
Toll Free: 800.2.BERLIN

## Effective Date

12/05/2012

At Berlin Packaging (“we” or “us”), we care about your privacy and personal information. The following privacy policy applies to all websites owned by Berlin Packaging (collectively, the “Websites”). IF YOU DO NOT ACCEPT THIS PRIVACY POLICY, PLEASE DO NOT ACCESS, USE, OR BROWSE OUR WEBSITES.

## Collection

We collect personal information about you, such as your name, credit card information, postal address, telephone, and email address when you voluntarily provide such information to us. We may collect personal information from you when you contact us using our online contact form or if you send us an email. We may also collect personal information from you if you choose to fill out one of our surveys or if you choose to register on one of our Websites.

We may also collect non-personal information from you when you visit or interact with our Websites, such as Internet Protocol (IP) address, browser type, data and time of visit, referral page, the pages you visit, and other information.

## Use

We use the personal information we collect about you to respond to your questions or to provide you with the products, services, or information that you request. We may also use your personal information to keep you informed about our new products and services offerings or to tell you about upcoming events. If you wish you opt-out of receiving promotional or marketing materials from us, please see the “Your Choices” section below.

We may use non-personal information to ensure the technical performance and functioning of the Websites and to personalize your experience on our Websites by delivering you more relevant content.

## Sharing

We may share your information among our affiliates, subsidiaries, employees, contractors, or consultants so that they may perform their duties and so that we can provide you with our products and services.

Generally, we will not sell, distribute, publish, disclose, or share your personal information to any unaffiliated third parties without your consent. In limited situations, though, we may disclose your personal information to unaffiliated third parties: (1) who provide services on our behalf to the extent such information is necessary to deliver their services; (2) in order to comply with law or respond to a legally valid inquiry or order or search warrant; (3) as part of a corporate transaction, such as a merger, or sale of assets; (4) in order to enforce our Terms & Conditions and other agreements or policies; or (5) to otherwise protect ourselves, our employees, our customers, or members of the public.

## Your Choices

If you wish to opt-out of receiving promotional or marketing materials from us, update or change your information, or delete personal information you provided to us, please let us know by either calling our toll free number 1.800.2.BERLIN, sending us an email at marketing@BerlinPackaging.com, or by writing to us at the mailing address at the top of this policy. Please provide us with your full name and address (or other applicable contact information) when contacting us.

Please note that it may take several days to process your opt-out request and that you may continue to receive promotional or marketing materials during this time. Also, please note that opting-out of receiving will not preclude us from sending you other types of non-promotional messages, such as emails about your registered account.

## Cookies and Other Web Technologies

Our Website uses cookies and other web technologies. A cookie is a small text file that is stored on your computer or device by a website’s server. When you visit or interact with our Websites, we may use cookies to improve your experience on our Website. For example, cookies help us understand whether or not you are already logged in as you click throughout our Website. We do not use cookies to collect and/or store your personal information. Most browsers have options that allow you to choose what cookies can be placed on your computer and to delete or disable cookies, but setting a browser to reject cookies may affect and limit your experience on our Websites.

## Children

Our Websites are not directed to children under the age of 13 and we do not knowingly collect personal information from children. If you are under the age of 13, please stop using our Websites. It is our policy not to knowingly solicit or permit children under the age of 13 to provide their personal information for any purpose.

## Third Party Websites and Social Networks

Our Websites may link to websites that are not under our control, and we are not responsible for the privacy practices of any linked site not controlled by us. For example, we provide a number of links to associations and institutes that are part of the packaging industry, as well as other industries. We also provide links to social networks, such as Facebook, Twitter, and LinkedIn. We are not responsible for the privacy practices at these external websites or their use of your information. We encourage you to review the privacy policies for these websites.

## Changes to this Privacy Policy

We may update our privacy policy at any time by posting updated text on this webpage. We display an Effective Date at the top of this policy so that it will be easier for you to know when there has been a change. Accordingly, we recommend that you check this privacy policy from time to time so that you are aware of our most current privacy practices. Each time you access, use, or browse one of our Websites, you signify your acceptance of the then-current version of this privacy policy.

## Questions or Comments

If you have any questions or comments about the information in this privacy policy, please let us know by either calling our toll free number 800.2.BERLIN, sending us an e-mail at marketing@BerlinPackaging.com or by writing to us at the mailing address at the top of the privacy policy.
